https://bh-co.com/beaird-harris-privacy-policy/

COVID-19 Resource Center
COVID-19 Update: Beginning May 18, we will begin cautiously reopening Beaird Harris. Read More.
If you have any questions, please reach out to your primary Beaird Harris contact or call (972) 503-1040.
Beaird Harris will be closed on Friday, July 3rd in observance of the Independence Day holiday.
Privacy Policy
The Beaird Harris privacy policy applies to former clients, as well as current clients of Beaird Harris. It also applies to individuals who disclose personal information to Beaird Harris in a consultation that does not culminate in the engagement of Beaird Harris as the client’s investment advisor or CPA.We do not sell information about current or former clients or their accounts to anyone.On occasion, we do share personal information between Beaird Harris Wealth Management, Inc. and Beaird Harris & Co., P.C. in an effort to gain “tax-perspective” and provide service to the client or provide information necessary to complete a tax return. We do not disclose nonpublic personal information to third parties unless one of the following limited exceptions applies.</strong >We disclose personal identifying information in order to complete certain transactions that you direct, such as the transfer of assets from another financial institution.We will release personal information in limited circumstances where permitted or required by law to do so, such as in cooperation with regulators or in response to a subpoena.We will release information about you if you direct us to do so.What Type of Information Do We Collect?When you engage Beaird Harris, you provide us with your nonpublic personal information. We collect and use this information to complete tax return(s), provide tax planning services, open investment account(s) and monitor your account(s) on an ongoing basis. The nonpublic personal information we collect falls into the following categories: Information we receive from you on your tax returns, source documents and/or account applications or other forms, such as your name, address, social security number, income, assets and other household information, as well as information regarding your financial goals, investment time horizon and risk tolerance. Information about your transactions, including balances, positions and account history.Confidentiality and SecurityOur employees are governed by a strict code of conduct and are required to maintain the confidentiality of our client’s information. We restrict access to information about you to the employees who need to know that information in order to service your account. Additionally, we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with Federal Standards to protect this information.Privacy Policy UpdatesPeriodically we may revise our privacy policy. We will not, however, revise our privacy policy to permit the sharing of nonpublic personal information other than as described in this notice unless we first notify you and provide you with an opportunity to prevent the information sharing.If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at 972-503-1040.
Beaird Harris12221 Merit Drive, Suite 750
Dallas, TX 75251
Map
Let's TalkPhone:
(972) 503-1040
Fax:
(972) 503-1120
Contact Us
Our TeamYou don't get just one advisor - you get our whole team!
Our Team
Follow UsLike social media? Receive and share insights in real time.
Linkedin-in
Twitter
Facebook
Youtube
